Mike Webb is running for congress in
Virginia's e8th District he recently
posted a screenshot of his desktop to
his Facebook page oh look he's got a lot
of tabs open clearly he's a busy guy
quick poll anyone not know where this is
going uh Jack activate thermal porn scan
beep oh no oh
no we have corn
T
So In addition to a Yahoo search and his
uh AT&T bill right here Mr Webb was also
very interested in Leela Rivera tight
booty and ivonne's sexy amateur so he's
into fitness and entrepreneurs that's
fantastic
now he's a politician naturally he had a
great explanation for the screen grab
faux PA he was just testing for
viruses is what he was doing he had the
porn sites open so he could scan for
viruses I maybe he was jering it to his
AT&T bill I don't know oh overages yeah
roll over minutes I don't
know I personally would I like why why
in this day and age do we feel like we
need to hide this from people like why
you know what why did he just come out
and go yeah I was cranking it to porn
you know I want to do a little genetic
re I want to do a little genetic
redistricting what's the problem do you
think do you think anyone would fault
him for that no one would fault him for
that I mean these are not insane
categories it's not crazy so I don't
understand look any candidate who
Embraces his love of the pornographic
Arts would thrive in today's political
landscape they'd be like wow what a
breath of fresh air based on what's
going on in the
election